# **Aaron Magder**

Hamilton, ON (289)-780-8981 aaron@magder.me

## Summary

Hard working self-motivator with many years of experience in the IT field. Currently holds a 96% average at Mohawk College with expectation to graduate by the end of 2015. Demonstrated strong technical skills and out-of-box problem solving. Proven leadership experience.

### Education

Network Engineering and IT Security Analyst Advanced Diploma

Mohawk College (2012-2015)
In progress (one semester remaining). Current GPA of 96% over 5 semesters. Been named to Dean's Honour List each

semester.

### Experience

ePortfolio Assistant

(Sep 2015 - Current)

Mohawk College

Web design of online portfolios.

**IT Technician** 

(Apr 2015 - Sep 2015)

Halton Hills Hydro

Troubleshooting a variety of issues on a small business network (approx 50 users). Backend support and server maintenance. Provided analysis of IDS reports. Designed an IDS. Developed software and web applications. Assisted with mobile device

configuration.

**Service Desk Analyst** 

(Apr 2014 – Sep 2014)

Ministry of Government Services

Troubleshooting a variety of issues on a large enterprise network

(approx 10,000 users). Fulfillment of service requests.

#### **Helpdesk Specialist**

(Nov 2010 - Sep 2012)

#### **Bell Mobility**

Troubleshooting a variety of issues for end users for a mobile service provider. Assisting internal agents with enterprise tools. Reporting and tracking of service outages.

### **Skills**

I am highly skilled in networking, security and administration of Windows/Linux networks. I have experience with a wide variety of technologies. If you'd like further detail about specific skillsets feel free to contact me.

TCP/IP Networking			
Network Security			
Windows Administration			
Linux Administration			
Mobile Devices			
Scripting/Programming/Web Dev			

### Certifications and Awards

Comptia A+ Certification 2008
Part 2 Winner – IBM Master the Mainframe Challenge 2014

## **Additional Information**

To view more information or to connect with me on social media visit:



http://magder.me